# Teresa Fogarty 3055 62<sup>nd</sup> Court, Vero Beach, FL 32966 (772) 834-3245

teresa92178@gmail.com teresa92178@gmail.com

# **Skills Summary:**

Experienced customer service and collections specialist, who consistently exceeds company goals. A top selling performer promoted to Regional Director in charge of district sales. Proficient at Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Office, QuickBooks, Medical Manager, and Medisoft.

#### **Career Experience:**

Dynix Diagnostix

Fort Pierce, FL

## Lead A/R

August 2017 to Present

- Reconciling and balancing weekly/monthly
- Inbound/Outbound collections calls. Including training other employees
- Mastered insurance verification, payment posting duties and was promoted to Lead.

### Harvest Food and Outreach

Vero Beach, FL

### Front Desk Receptionist (On the job training)

August 2015 to Present

- · Greeting clients and directing them to the appropriate resources
- Handle incoming calls and take messages
- · Oversee and mentor children at risk who attend the after school program
- · Preparing mailings, making photocopies and performing other clerical duties as needed

# Genaissance Pharmaceuticals

Yale-New Haven, CT

#### **Collections Specialist**

March 2006 to November 2007

- Collected account balances from all responsible parties
- · Identified major payer/billing issues, resolved declined, and unpaid insurance accounts
- Surpassed monthly goals while maintaining compliance with all HIPAA requirements
- Daily activities included working accounts receivable reports, mail, calls, faxes, and emails

# Nationwide Expos

Key West, FL

# Sales Representative/Regional Director

February 2002 to October 2005

- Completed formal training in sales for a nationwide call center
- Handled heavy call volume dealing directly with other companies by negotiating terms and contracts
- Consulted with customers and supported them with their issues and concerns
- Promoted to Regional Director in charge of district sales
- Payment entry, managed company statistics, tracked unpaid claims, and supervised team/schedules

# Radiology Regional Center

Fort Myers, FL

# **Patient Account Representative**

July 1999 to November 2001

- Actively worked on the Accounts Receivable team, which was responsible for over 37,500 Patient accounts in various age categories
- Recovered maximum amount of past due funds while still answering patient questions, concerns, and complaints regarding their bills

# Education:

Molloy College

Rockville Centre, NY

Certified Medical Biller/Coder

1996

Significant courses included: CPT and ICD-9 coding, Medical Terminology, Biology and Anatomy, and Medicare and Medicaid seminars.

Department of Children and Families Training and Development